# KYLA MEDINA

#### INTERACTION DESIGNER AND TECHNOLOGIST



# **ABOUT**

I'm a friendly multidisciplinary designer working in sunny New York City. In constant pursuit of new artistic and technical skills, I'm interested in applying digital technology to aesthetic experiences. My wide range of skills allows me to work through all phases of design and with each new project, I aim to create engaging experiences through creative uses of technology, new media, and storytelling. Offline, you can find me biking around the city, gallery hopping, or working on a photography project.

# **EDUCATION**

# U OF IOWA | COGNITIVE SCIENCE AND DIGITAL ARTS CONCENTRATION: PHOTOGRAPHY AND DESIGN

# **SKILLS**

**UX** | Axure, UXPin, OmniGraffle**DESIGN** | Indesign, Photoshop, Illustrator, Sketch

**PROTOTYPING** | Framer Studio, Invision, After Effects

**CODE** | HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Xcode

#### REFERENCES

### SARA THOMPSON | SENIOR PRODUCT DESIGNER

Free Association 541.910.7465 sara@freeassociation.is

# GABBY BURLESON | SENIOR VISUAL DESIGNER

Critical Mass 307.325.4940 gabby@criticalmass.com

# TIFFANY HUFFORD | SENIOR PROJECT MANAGER

Huge 419.345.7876 hufford.24@gmail.com

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### CREATIVE TECHNOLOGIST | MAKEABLE

NEW YORK CITY, MAY 2013 - PRESENT

I work at all stages of production, from creative concept to final delivery. Depending on the needs of a project, I've worked as the visual designer, interaction designer/ developer, and/or photographer. Working in this fast-paced, agile environment, I've been fortunate enough to design the UX for Cognizant, prototype for The Weather Channel, create the visual direction for American Kennel Club, and photograph for Free Association. Alongside a brilliant team, I've worked collaboratively on many unique and challenging projects; from e-commerce solutions to mobile apps to dynamic, content-driven, responsive websites.

#### VISUAL DESIGNER | ARTNET

NEW YORK CITY, SEPT 2011 - MAY 2013

As part of Artnet's marketing team, I was lead designer on all digital and print design initiatives. I worked alongside strategists and copywriters to ideate and create new marketing campaigns for Artnet and its partners. Finished products included digital and print collateral, email campaigns, and websites. I also coded the digital marketing campaigns and worked with the technology team to create the UX and design for new site features.

## **DESIGNER** | TEMPORAMA STUDIO

IOWA CITY, MAY 2010 - AUG 2011

I worked autonomously on a range of projects for this new media art studio that included graphic design, video editing, photography, research, and web design.